

TRAN LY NAM

JAVA DEVELOPER

Male



0931967923



Jan 02, 1988

tranlynam@gmail.com

9

152 Nguyen Huu Dat street, Tay Thanh ward, Tan Phu district, Ho Chi Minh city.

"

I am Tran Ly Nam, a Java Developer with a good knowledge of OOP, Data Structure, Algorithm and Java Web. Besides I also have a basic knowledge of HTML, CSS and JavaScript.

With the ability to work independently or in teams, I can support and learn from my leaders as well as my teammates to achieve our goals effectively.

I aim to be a good and skillful employee. I am also willing to constantly cultivate knowledge, experience and approach new technologies in a positive way.

Education

• 05/2022 - 04/2022: **FUNIX Online Education**

Major: Object-Oriented Programming in Java

Completed Subjects:

- 1. Building The First Website. GPA: 9.2
- 2. Programming in JavaScript. GPA: 8.4
- 3. Object Oriented Programming in Java. GPA: 8.8
- 4. Data Structure and Algorithm. GPA: 7.6
- 5. Database Systems. GPA: 9.6
- 6. Web Application Development. GPA: 8.6
- 7. End Term Project. GPA: 8.5

09/2006 - 04/2011: University Of Technology

Major: Environmental Engineering. GPA: 7.37/10

Certifications

2018: TESOL

(Madison School of Professional Development)

2009: TOEIC Certificate. Score: 810

(ETS)

Objectives

- Within 1 year: Junior Developer.

- From 2 to 4 years: Senior Developer.

- After 4 years: Technical Leader.

Skills

- Front-end and Back-end:

HTML/CSS, JavaScript and Java.

- Algorithm and Data structure:

Types of sorting, LinkedList, Queue, Stack, Binary Tree and Graph.

- Database:

MS SQL Server.

- Java Web:

Servlet, JSP, Java beans, HTML form, JDBC, JNDI, JSTL and Spring MVC

framework.

Work experience

Outerspace Language School, Teacher

Feb 2018 - Present

Teach Communicative English to teenagers and adults.

Home, Tutor

Oct 2014 - Feb 2018

Teach English to secondary and high school students.

TECHGEL Company, Project Engineer

May 2011 - Oct 2014

- Manage and file documents
- Communicate with supervisors and investors in English.

Course Projects

1. Building a website:

May 25 - May 29

- Techniques: HTML, CSS and Bootstrap.
- Links:
 - + https://github.com/lynam88/Web-Design
 - + https://lynam88.github.io/Web-Design/

2. Developing a news application:

Jun. 25 - Jun. 28

- Techniques: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery and Bootstrap.
- Link: https://github.com/lynam88/News-App

3. Developing a human - resource app:

Jul. 21 - Jul. 25

- Technique: Java.
- Link: https://github.com/lynam88/Human-Resources

4. Designing a searching - sorting program:

Aug. 16 - Aug. 19

- Techniques: Bubble Sort, Selection Sort, Insertion Sort, Linear Search and Binary Search.
- Link: https://github.com/lynam88/Basic-Search-Sort

5. Designing a management program:

Aug. 24 - Aug. 31

- Techniques: LinkedList, Recursion, Stack and Queue.
- Link: https://github.com/lynam88/Product-Management

References

Ms. Oanh

Funix Mentor

Mobile: 0981368808

Ms. Vy

Funix Hannah

Mobile:

0706168094

Interests

- Listening to music.
- Reading books.
- Traveling...

Course Projects (cont.)

6. SQL Query Data:

Oct. 3 - Oct. 5

- Technique: SQL.
- Link:

https://github.com/lynam88/Databa se-Management-System

7. Building an Ecommerce Website:

Nov. 13 - Nov. 20

- Technique: Java Web.
- Link:

https://github.com/lynam88/Web-Application-Development

8. Building a Donation Website:

Dec. 13 - Apr. 14

- Technique: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, SQL and Java Web.
- Link:

https://github.com/lynam88/Do An Funix